# Olesia Pryhun

## Junior front-end developer

#### **PORTFOLIO**

My detailed **portfolio** with pet projects: <a href="https://pryhun.me">https://pryhun.me</a>.

My GitHub account: <a href="https://github.com/Olesia-P">https://github.com/Olesia-P</a>.

My <u>last project</u>: fake online shop with a local Next.js API, connected to MongoDB.

#### **ABOUT ME**

I finished a front-end course, then I continued my studies with a mentor (experienced web developer). He provided me with support and guidance throughout the whole process.

I learned through building projects, making mistakes and fixing them. I used all tools possible: from docs and forums to YouTube and ChatGPT.

#### SKILLS

#### Front-end: Back-end

- MongoDB
- Next.js API React
- Redux

Next.js

- Bootstrap
- Sass/Scss
- Java Script
- CSS
- HTML

#### Other

- Postman



- Git + Bash
- **ESLint**



- +380681250102 (Telegram, Viber)
- pryhun.o@gmail.com
- Telegram: @Pryhun Olesia
- <u>LinkedIn</u>

#### LOCATION

- Ukraine, Kyiv
- Or remote work

### LANGUAGE

- English C1 (CAE Certificate)
- Ukrainian (native)

#### **EDUCATION**

Online front-end course (SheCodes)

2023

**Online QA Manual course** (Hillel)

2022

**Kyiv National Linguistic** University

Bachelor of Language and Literature (Japanese)

2015 - 2019

#### HOBBIES

- Jigsaw puzzles
- Coloring books
- Board games

### **EXPERIENCE**

Studying web development

2022-2024

2019-2022

**English Teacher** 

Language courses

• I taught teenagers and adults English, individually and in groups, offline and online.